I wish I could afford a new car.
>> I wish we could afford this one.
>> [laughter]
>> We should have told our house since we
[clears throat] were going.
>> I thought we decided we wouldn't.
>> You decided we wouldn't.
>> I'm the breadwinner. I have to make
these executive decisions.
>> [laughter]
>> She's family.
You can't just pretend she's not there.
>> I always think it's worth a try.
>> [laughter]
>> Anyway, she can't complain.
We've left father in good hands.
>> You think she'll really think our Rose
qualifies as good hands?
>> All right. We've left your father in
good legs.
>> Hello, Flo.
Do you think this little holiday will
bring us closer together?
>> [laughter]
>> How close do you want to get?
When I did Bruce's drains yesterday, I
let you help me with the rods, didn't I?
>> [laughter]
>> When I said we ought to do things
together more, I didn't mean drains.
>> Daisy, we've had our differences, but
when you get right down to it, there
isn't anyone I'd rather have helping me
with the drains.
>> That's sweet.
I think I think that's really sweet.
You always were a smooth talker when you
wanted to be.
>> [laughter]
>> Traveling light, Richard?
>> I told her it's too much.
>> I'm good job you're not going by air.
>> By air? I'm beginning to wonder if the
ship's big enough.
>> I do hope you have a splendid time,
Richard.
>> Thanks,
>> Ready for the off?
>> She's almost ready. She's taking endless
trouble. She remembers the newsreels of
how people used to dress FOR LUXURY
LINERS.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> A FILM STAR?
OH,
thank you, dear.
It's probably just a coincidence.
>> [laughter]
>> Goodbye, my dear friends.
Emma, be brave. I shall return.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh, dear. I do fluster him so.
I believe I disturb HIM VERY POWERFULLY.
>> [laughter]
>> ARE YOU SURE THIS IS THE right way?
>> But yes, of course I am, dear.
>> Wait a minute. We're in Surrey now, and
we're going down to Hampshire.
>> Yes, that's right.
>> But you've got the map open at Norfolk.
>> Huh?
>> [laughter]
>> Near King's Lynn.
AGAIN!
>> RICHARD, LOOK OUT!
>> [laughter]
>> AREN'T YOU SUPPOSED TO SLOW DOWN WHEN
YOU go through one of these?
>> [laughter]
>> Why weren't you concentrating, dear? I
cannot imagine.
>> [laughter]
>> I think water's got into the system.
>> What?
What does that mean?
>> It means that we're stuck.
>> Don't be silly, Richard. We can't be
stuck. We have an appointment with the
QE2.
We'll have to go and get some help.
>> But the water.
>> Well, it can't be that deep.
Take your shoes and socks off. Roll your
trousers up.
>> [laughter]
>> Come on, dear. Quick's the word, SHARP'S
THE MOTION.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> RICHARD,
A LITTLE DECORUM, PLEASE. As befits
someone with a reservation for a quality
cruise.
>> [laughter]
>> A little faster, Richard, please.
Close the door, dear. There's a terrible
draft.
>> [laughter]
>> This can't be right.
>> It's a shortcut.
>> [laughter]
>> We're lost.
>> Of course we're not lost. We're here.
>> Well, we can't be there because that's a
B road.
>> Well, then this must be the B road.
>> This isn't even a road.
>> Richard.
>> [laughter]
>> Richard, I hope you're not going to be
in this unreasonable mood for the entire
holiday.
Now, please, drive on.
I'm sure you'll find we come to the road
we need.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh, there's a late night floor show.
>> Oh, no.
>> Oh, it'll be fun, dear. Singing,
dancing, a touch of comedy.
>> No, look.
>> Hm?
>> [laughter]
>> Well, it's obvious to me what's
happened, dear.
You've taken THE WRONG TURNING.
>> [laughter]
>> IT'S BIGGER THAN YOU THINK.
LESS NOISE, TALKING.
>> [laughter]
>> Excuse me, sir. You're wanted in the
director's room.
>> All right, thank you.
Will you be all right up there?
>> Fine.
>> All right, I'll join you again in a
minute.
Daisy, do you want to come up here and
have a look?
>> I'm not coming up there. This is not the
kind of skirt you can climb ladders in.
Not that you've even noticed.
>> Now, don't start that again. One whiff
of salt air and you go bananas.
>> I thought a cruise was supposed to be
romantic.
>> IT'S NOT COMPULSORY.
>> [laughter]
>> I KNEW YOU WERE WRONG. We should have
turned left.
>> I did turn left.
>> Perhaps you'll follow my directions in
future.
>> following them. You said turn left.
>> This must lead to a deck.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> What is it?
>> The shame, Richard, the shame.
>> Just turning right when it should have
been left is not all that bad.
>> No, it's all that, dear.
It's almost London, Daisy.
>> What about them?
>> They're here.
>> But how can they be here?
>> Well, they are.
I've just seen them climbing out of a
lifeboat.
They must HAVE STOWED AWAY.
>> [laughter]
>> OH, RICHARD.
MY own sister, a stowaway.
>> Well, Daisy, maybe, but but do you think
Onslow would get up early enough to be a
stowaway?
>> [laughter]
>> Are
Are you absolutely sure?
>> They were hiding in a lifeboat. How else
would Onslow gain access to the QE2?
>> Perhaps he's won some money on the
horses.
>> No, Onslow never wins on the horses.
You've seen the way he dresses. Does he
look as if he wins on the horses?
The horses dress BETTER THAN ONSLOW.
>> [laughter]
>> WELL, WHAT'S HE wearing now?
>> Well, I mean, he looks quite smart at
the moment. He's trying to bluff his way
through, trying to look like a
passenger.
Oh, but my poor sister,
sleeping in a lifeboat,
cowering like some criminal on this
magnificent ship.
>> [laughter and gasps]
>> At this very moment, probably hiding in
some forgotten corner of the bilges.
>> Good evening.
>> Good evening, madam, sir.
>> Good evening, Mr. and Mrs. Bouquet.
>> Just one moment, please, madam.
Are you sure you're in this dining room,
madam? This is reserved for first-class
passengers. I think you'll find you
should be in the Mauritania restaurant.
>> No, but there there there must be some
mistake.
>> Excuse me.
Good evening, sir.
>> Good evening. Fine, thank you very much.
>> Let's not debate it now.
Look, there are some places at the
captain's table.
>> Those are reserved for the captain's
guests, madam. Ah, here they come now.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> They're doing pretty well for stowaways.
>> [laughter]
>> We've got to find out what's going on,
Richard.
>> Can we have dinner first?
>> [laughter]
>> You can do what you like, dear. I've
lost my appetite.
You somehow have to contact Daisy and
Onslow as soon as you've eaten.
>> [laughter]
>> Well,
>> they're here officially.
>> What do you mean, officially?
>> Your brother-in-law has won first prize
in a newspaper competition.
Two tickets for this cruise with all the
trimmings.
>> [laughter]
>> Why didn't they say something? Why
didn't they tell us?
>> Onslow said he didn't want to make us
jealous.
You should see their cabin. It is
magnificent.
It is really luxurious. Champagne,
flowers,
they're being treated like film stars.
>> All right. ALL RIGHT. [screaming] ALL
RIGHT.
>> WHAT?
THE COACH LEAVES IN AN HOUR.
I'VE BEEN A BAD OLD DAY, HAVEN'T I?
>> NO.
It's been all right, bro. It's been all
right.
I've really enjoyed myself.
I'm feeling a bit cream crackered now,
though.
I think I might have a touch of that
yuppie flu, you know?
>> Yeah?
It may sound if they would have lobster
vindaloo and full-time pina coladas,
could it?
>> It might have slowed me down a bit,
yeah.
>> [laughter]
[clears throat]
>> Went down to the cemetery yesterday.
Put some flowers on Mom's grave.
I haven't been down there lately,
though, has
It's something to do, you know? No, no,
it's all right. Well, then she
understands. She knows that you still
think about her. Yeah, of course I do.
No, I just, you know, I was um
I just had, you know, I was like
chatting and that.
Just letting her know what's been
happening.
I bet she was well pleased. Mhm.
You know, your old Cassandra, she
reminds me a bit of Mom, you know?
Yeah, good.
She's got drive, isn't she? You know,
that's one thing Mom had. You know, Mom
had a lot of drive.
Yeah.
Cassandra's very ambitious.
No, it's good, isn't it?
Mhm, cool.
I think it's in the way of her career.
I don't know about that.
You must be well pleased.
Yeah.
Cuz she's an achiever.
Yeah. Yeah.
She's a bit like me in many ways.
Yeah, I suppose she is.
I've always been an achiever.
I never actually achieved nothing, mind
you, but
I give it a shout.
There it is.
This reminds me of the time that me and
Jumbo Mills
set up a seafood stall outside the Nick
Zedd.
Here was on wheels, we called it.
>> [laughter]
>> Who is going to build empires, you know.
You know, every pub in London was going
to have a seafood stall outside called
the Eels on Wheels.
You know what I said to him the night
that we came up with the scheme?
>> This time next year we'll be
millionaires.
>> I said, "This time next year we'll be
millionaires."
And we could have been, Rodney.
>> Could have been.
>> You know what killed off Eels on Wheels,
Rodney?
It's television.
>> What, the Cook Report?
>> No, no, no.
When television starts humanizing fish
>> What are you going on about?
>> Well, they did, they started to make
fish human.
You know, first of all there was that
shark thing.
Flipper.
You have got no disease, have you?
Then there was Squidly Diddly, the
octopus, you know, who played the drums.
Then there was Michael Fish.
>> What has he got to do with this?
>> He's charm, telling you. Mothers used to
come round complaining that their kids
refused to eat our homemade fish fingers
in case they was related to the Man from
Atlantis.
>> [laughter]
>> And that report from the council health
inspector didn't help none, either.
Could have made it though, bro.
Could have.
We will do.
We will.
Never stop believing, eh, bro?
Never stop believing.
Are we all here now, Del?
>> No, we're just waiting for Rodney. He's
reporting in to headquarters.
Okay, it's me.
>> Rodney, I've been waiting for your call
all day.
>> Have you?
>> So, how are you?
>> Oh, we're fine.
Listen, we're at the coach park. We'll
be off in a couple of minutes.
Yeah. You won't tell Marlene about what
happened, will you, Del?
I'll get the bullet if he found out
about this.
>> Leave it out, Harry. What sort of bloke
do you think I am?
>> I had one glass of lemonade in that pub.
I don't know what happened.
I felt strange.
It was as if I'd been overcome by fumes
or something.
>> Yeah, well, whatever it was,
it's lucky we had Denzil about, wasn't
it, mate?
>> Oh, no, he's a good bloke, that Denzil.
>> Good bloke.
He's one of the best.
>> One of the very best.
>> Del!
>> What does that dipstick want now?
>> Smoke coming from the radio.
>> Well, you must have pressed the wrong
button or something.
Oh, look, I'll come and sort it out.
So, how's your day been?
>> Oh, usual sort of thing. Oh, Steven
phoned this morning.
>> Did he?
>> Yeah, he found that holiday brochure
you'd been telling us about. Mummy
called round to see if I'd like to have
some lunch with her. Then the Kent
Police Constabulary phoned to confirm
that you lived at this address.
>> That was nice of them, wasn't it?
>> It's not supposed to do that, is it?
>> No.
Well, it wasn't in the brochure, at
least.
Oi, Boyce, see?
Boyce, see? Here. Come here a minute.
>> Yes, what is it?
>> Look, you see?
Del said, "Give me the ball."
>> I might have guessed Del would be behind
it somewhere.
>> No, he didn't mean to get me into
trouble.
>> Well, he never does, does he? Yet, it
seems every time Del is around you,
something goes wrong and you're at the
sticky end of it.
>> Not every time.
>> What are we supposed to do about it?
>> Well, I'd switch it off if I was you,
Del. The main petrol line runs right
underneath there.
>> Rodney.
Oi, Del.
Babe, we got to do something ABOUT THIS.
>> SOMEONE GET SOME WATER.
>> GOOD IDEA. WATER, WE NEED LOADS OF
WATER.
>> AND IS COACH fitted with a fire
extinguisher?
>> I found him, Come on, get off
there.
>> And what about that time he entered one
of your paintings in a competition and
you won first prize in the under 15
category?
>> Yes, I do seem to recollect it, but I
don't think you
>> And I had to spend a week in Majorca
>> posing as your common-law stepmother.
>> Come on, then, EVERYBODY. HURRY UP, NOT
RODNEY.
>> All right.
Look, I agree that Del gets a bit out of
hand,
but I think it's unfair to say that
everything he touches goes wrong.
>> [applause]
>> Our coach has just blown up.
Don't worry, Rodney. I won't tell your
governor about it.
>> Rodney.
Look, come on. It's only a quarter past
eight.
Let's whip down the old Mardi Gras, have
a couple of couple of jars, you know,
scampi supper, eh? What do you reckon?
What do you reckon?
>> No. Look, I promised Cassandra I
wouldn't go out and I intend to keep
that promise.
>> Do you reckon she believed you?
About what?
When you said you would go out on the
town.
>> Well, of course she believed me.
>> Why?
Nothing.
Uncle, you're not trying to suggest that
Cassandra thought that Roddy was going
out on the razzle that she would go out
on the razzle as well, are you?
>> What do you mean what's good for the
goose is good for the gander?
>> Yeah.
>> No.
>> Uh.
>> Cassandra wouldn't have gone out.
>> How do you know that?
>> Because I haven't gone out.
>> Yeah, but how does she know that?
>> [laughter]
>> Beca-
She just does, right? Our marriage is
based on trust.
>> [clears throat]
>> Yeah, he's right.
Cassandra wouldn't go out and join us
up.
>> Thank you.
>> She wouldn't have to. She's got the flat
to herself.
So what?
>> No, no, I just
No, I just meant if she felt a bit
lonely,
she could invite someone round.
Yeah.
Like that couple at your wedding
anniversary, Steven and his wife.
So what's wrong with that?
>> Nothing, nothing. No, it'd be a nice bit
of company for Cassandra.
>> She said we get on well with that
Steven.
>> Of course they get on well. They work
together at the bank. He is a colleague.
In fact, he's more than a colleague.
He's on top.
He's our immediate superior.
>> No, anyway, she couldn't have invited
them two round cuz Steven's wife's gone
away for the weekend, you remember?
>> Oh, yeah.
If that Steven's been round my flat,
I'll kill him.
Oh, what put that idea in your head?
I don't know. It's
just something's been bugging me. Well,
what do you want to do? Do you want to,
you know,
pop out for a drink and sort of talk
about it? Hm?
Might make you feel better, Rodney.
Yeah, well, I suppose I could manage a
This is a conspiracy, isn't it? You two
are in league with each other, aren't
you? You just want me to come to the
nightclub with you, and you want to beat
you yourself. Well, it ain't going to
work. I promised Cassandra I would not
go out, and I'm not going out. All
right? All right, all right, keep your
hair on.
Oh, I was only teasing you. I wouldn't
have any harm. All right. Well, let's
just shut up about it and get some
sleep.
Do you have an extra blanket? I'm
freezing in here. Yeah, it is a bit
cold, isn't it?
Cold? You bits of kids don't know the
meaning of the word.
You should have been with me on the
Russian convoys.
One night it was so cold the flame on my
lighter froze.
>> [laughter]
>> Come on, then, just one quick light out.
Where have I seen that bird before?
Say, Sol, what's her name?
The one you went out with for a while,
Del. It's Raquel, the stripper gram. No,
it is not. It is too.
Hm? You look at the board. The Great
Raimondo and Raquel. [music]
It is a
>> [applause]
[applause]
[applause and music]
[laughter]
[applause]
>> Raquel!
DELL!
ALL RIGHT.
BLOODY [music] CLEVER, DELL.
SO, I GOT BACK TO ENGLAND ABOUT 6 months
ago.
I wasn't sure what to do with myself.
[music]
I haven't got any family, except a
brother in Milton Keynes, but we haven't
spoken for years.
So, I saw my [music] agent, and she tied
me in with Ray.
>> Ray?
>> The great Ramondo.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> He was working in a holiday camp down in
Devon. His last assistant had walked out
on him.
>> [music]
>> Well,
he's a bit of a pig.
Anyway, after that we got a 3-month
contract here.
Well, it's not much, but it's a job.
Keeps a roof over my head.
>> Yeah.
I didn't mean to let you down, you know.
I mean, I was on my way round to you
when I was
unexpectedly arrested. [music]
>> I know. It's all right, you already
explained.
>> Why didn't you write to me?
>> Write to you?
I thought you'd dumped me.
I got pride, Dell.
Never written to the other blokes who've
dumped me, and I wasn't starting with
you.
>> Do you want another drink?
>> No, I'm back on stage in a little while.
It's been no one else.
I mean, since we split up, I haven't
you know, not been interested.
>> No, no, not me.
No, no, honest.
>> Yeah, all right, I believe you.
>> Anyway, what you going to do, uh,
you know, when this contract's finished?
>> I'm leaving the act.
I can't stand Ray anymore.
He's got a temper. Sometimes he
frightens me.
Don't know where I'll go.
>> Peckham's very nice this time of year.
>> Is it?
>> I know a lovely little flat you can stay
at and all.
>> Well,
maybe I'll try Peckham then.
Thanks.
>> Raquel,
would you give me your autograph?
>> Get out.
>> No,
I mean, straight honest.
>> I've never given an autograph before.
>> Well, look, it's easy.
All you've got to do, look, is just
write your name.
And your address.
And your telephone number.
Hello.
Yeah, that's Peckham coach.
It's straight us out there.
Oh, sorry about this, Raquel.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, that's okay. So, what happened?
>> Well, the old girl where we were
staying, she locks her doors at 11:00.
Well, I mean, we didn't leave your
nightclub till gone 1:00, did we?
>> Well, I'm afraid an armchair and a
settee is the best I can offer you.
>> Oh, no, yeah, that's that's great.
That's lovely. Yeah, thanks a
Well,
no, this that'll be lovely, Raquel.
Yeah, it's all right, though. We'll be
away first thing in the morning cuz our
new coach comes about 9:00.
Mrs. Sweetheart, won't you give us
something to warm the old cockles, can
you?
>> Yeah, okay.
I'll make you a coffee.
>> Oh, yeah, Kirsty. Kirsty.
She's a blinding bird, isn't she,
Rodney, eh?
>> What, Raquel? She's terrific, though.
>> She's got radiant smile. Have you
noticed that?
>> What, a radiant smile?
>> Yeah.
>> We got to miss it, can you? I mean, you
know.
I mean, when she walks in, she
Well, she lights up a room.
>> Yeah.
Most of your birds walk in and light up
a
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah.
Yeah, she's straight as a die, you know.
Straight as a die. She don't mess around
with other blokes, you know.
>> What, you saying Cassandra does?
>> No, no, of course not. No, I've got
nothing against the girl.
>> That's all right, then, cuz if I thought
you
Sorry.
>> You're a touchy little git sometimes,
aren't you, eh? What I was just saying
was that since Raquel met me, she hasn't
been out with any other blokes.
>> But she only met you 2 hours ago.
>> [laughter]
>> NO, DON'T MEAN THIS TIME. I mean, like
the first time.
>> Oh, right.
>> She has been true unto me.
Raquel, what's all the noise?
THE GREAT RAMONDO!
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> WHAT AM I DOING HERE?
>> WE WAS LOCKED out of our digs and Raquel
said we could spend the night here, but
we're going to go to sleep.
>> Oh, did she? We'll see about that.
Raquel, WHAT'S THE IDEA OF LETTING
STRANGERS IN THE FLAT WITHOUT EVEN
ASKING ME?
>> I'M GOING TO KILL HIM.
>> NO, STAY CALM, DEREK.
>> It's going TO TAKE A BLOODY GOOD surgeon
3 or 4 hours to get HIS MAGIC WAND BACK.
>> OI, OI, OI, OI, OI.
NOW, come on, calm down.
>> I want to KNOW WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON
HERE.
>> DOWN.
>> LOOK, I'M NOT HAVING ANY MORE OF THIS.
>> NOW, LOOK, THIS
>> PROBABLY a perfectly simple explanation
to this.
>> Like what?
>> Well, HOW THE HELL SHOULD I KNOW?
>> There is a simple explanation, Rodney.
The Great Ramondo's a bleeding bully
boy. RAQUEL TOLD ME. HE'S GOT HER
TRAPPED HERE. IF SHE DON'T PLAY BALL
with him, not only has she lost her job,
but she's lost HER HOME AS WELL.
THAT'S BLACKMAIL, AND I DON'T LIKE THAT
sort of thing. I'M GOING TO SORT IT OUT
RIGHT NOW.
>> OI, OI. YOU'RE NOT CERTAIN OF ANYTHING.
DON'T JUMP TO CONCLUSIONS.
LOOK, for all you know, them two might
be
For ALL YOU KNOW.
>> WHAT?
>> I don't know.
>> [laughter]
>> Look,
just find out what the situation is
first, right? Nice and easy, Del, right?
Nice and easy.
Right?
Right, well, I'm just going to go in
there.
I just want to ask a few questions, and
you know, like that's all.
>> And what happens if you don't like the
answers?
>> Well, that's life, isn't it, eh?
Just I'll know where I stand, then,
won't I? Eh?
Eh?
All right.
Excuse me. I'm terribly sorry to bother
you. I just wondered if we could have a
little chat, see if we could come to
some sort of a an understanding. RIGHT.
>> [laughter]
>> THAT'S THE WAY, DEL. NICE AND EASY.
>> I DIDN'T EXPECT you back this early.
>> No, well,
here I am.
Cass, can we have a talk?
>> I don't think this is an appropriate
time, Rodney. Maybe later.
>> Look, I really think we ought to sit
down and discuss ex-
>> [laughter]
>> It's again.
What are you doing here?
>> I don't know.
I was just passing.
So, how was
Margate?
>> Forget Margate. What are you doing in my
flat?
>> Hey.
Back off, Rod.
I mean
what's the problem?
>> Rodney, what's wrong?
>> Well, I'll tell you the problem, shall
I?
It's something I've really wanted to do
for a long time, but I I've never got
round to it. So,
let me run this past you, Steven.
Try and get your HEAD ROUND THIS.
NOW, DO YOU GET MY WAY I'M COMING FROM,
OKAY, BUDDY?
>> [laughter]
[cheering]
>> I'M STEVEN.
PUNCH ME ON THE NOSE.
BUT, what's she doing here?
>> [laughter]
>> I thought she was going away for the
weekend to her parents.
>> She was, but there was a rail strike.
Joanne brought this holiday brochure
round for us.
>> [laughter]
>> Do you see anything in IT YOU LIKE?
>> HELLO, SWEETHEART.
HOW ARE YOU TODAY?
OH, GOOD.
How is the great Ramondo?
Oh, yeah. Well, I'm sure in his heart of
hearts he understood.
Yeah, we've been back about an hour.
Yeah.
Hm?
No, everyone's all right. Mhm.
We dropped her Rodney off at his house
yet.
Cassandra?
Nah, she'll be all right.
She'll be as good as gold.
Rodney's a bit of a charmer on the
quiet.
Nah, he knows how to handle situations.
>> [laughter]
>> Yes, I know sometimes I wish I was a bit
more like him and all.
Yeah.
I hope that I hope he's feeling much
better now.
Yeah?
Oh, didn't you hear?
He got a whack ON THE HEAD.
>> [laughter]
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW.
A STRANGEST THING, he was lying in BED
LAST NIGHT
>> [laughter]
>> WHEN ALL OF A SUDDEN A ROCK came flying
THROUGH THE WINDOW.
>> [laughter]
>> AND IT CAUGHT HIM A GLANCING blow on the
head.
I don't know, it's a mystery.
>> [laughter]
>> No mystery to me.
Daddy, your mate's done it. That should
be locked [laughter] up.
That's right, Aunt. That is absolutely
right, yeah. Tell her what happened to
Boyce and Mike when they was walking
home from the nightclub. Yeah. Well,
what was that?
Someone chucked a suitcase THROUGH A
WINDOW.
>> [laughter]
>> CAUGHT MIKE right on the shoulder.
FORTUNATELY, BOYCE'S HEAD BROKE ITS
FALL.
IT'S A TERRIBLE OLD WORLD, ISN'T IT,
SWEETHEART?
LISTEN, RAQUEL.
RAQUEL, you have to forgive me now,
aren't you, sweetheart?
How good. You don't make sense.
Uh listen,
I was [snorts] thinking about taking the
van out for a test drive next Saturday.
Well, I'm fitting a new radio, yeah.
I was
thinking I might go down to Margate.
I wouldn't be in a hurry to get home.
I was just wondering uh if you could get
the Great Romondo to do a disappearing
act.
Oh. Cushdy.
Yeah.
Oh, that's great. Yeah, all right,
darling.
I'll see you next next Saturday,
sweetheart.
Yeah. All right, bye for now. Bye.
Lovely jubbly.
Oi, what's your game? You want a cup of
tea? Go and make one, you lazy old sod.
GO ON.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> MHM.